Bradley Erskine

bradley.erskine75@gmail.com

%+64 22 170 1613

© 27A Guildford Street Burnside, Christchurch 8053



https://github.com/brad-skine

Summary

I have recently finished my Degree with a major in Computer Science and a minor in Mathematics. I am a passionate programmer who enjoys solving problems and over-coming challengers. I excel at team collaboration but can also get work done independently. I am always keen to learn more and am very passionate about data science, data engineering and machine learning.

Current Projects

Portfolio Website

7 July 2023 - Present Ð

2024 - Present

Have created a portfolio website to showcase my recent projects and acheivements. This shows my ability to design and optimise user experience.

Schedule planning application

Creating a mobile application that makes it easy to set and view goals. Manage a calander and set tick of daily task. I am learning how to use UML and to deploy applications on the play store.

Multiplayer tower defense game

Dec 2023 - Present Am creating a game where each players goal is defend their own base while attacking their opponents.

- · Learning how to implement networking learnt from Uni papers
- · Constantly overcoming problems and challengers
- · Implementing software design patters

Work Experience

Engineering project Fonterra

m Dec 2021 - Feb 2023

- · Conducted safety inspections of 160 ladders and updated safety documentation
- · Put information in tidy tables and graphs in Microsoft Excel
- Performed research on ladder safety standards and best practices.
- · Inspected and documented asbestos containment on site.
- · Compiled and organized data into spreadsheets for reporting and compliance.

Data Entry

Mov 2022 - Febuary 2023

- Transcribed hand-written materials into digital documents.
- · Converted data from paper to digital spreadsheets.
- · Summarized information quickly and accurately.
- Scanned documents and managed various office tasks.
- · Gained efficiency in typing accurately.

Domino's delivery driver and in store Aug 2021 - Feb 2022

- · Prepared pizzas and handled checkout operations.
- · Time management skills to deliver pizzas in time.
- Developed strong customer service and teamwork skills
- · Maintained cleanliness and hygiene standards.

Achievements

- Trinity Rock and Pop Grade 6, 7 and 8 playing the Electric guitar
- · Won South Island under 19 team even 2019
- Have compted for Southland and Otago at Nationals for Badminton

Education

Bachelor of Science

Feb 2021 - Dec 2024

University of Canterbury

Major in Computer Science, Minor in Mathematics.

Skills

General Skills

- Financial Analysis
- · Data Analytics
- Microsoft tools
- Debugging
- · Fast touch typing
- · Human computer Interaction

Software Development

- Scrum
- · Agile methodologies
- Github version control
- · Test Driven Development

Data

- Panda
- · Big data cleaning
- scikit-learn Dask
- NumPy

Programming Languages

- · Python3
- HTML

ML ops

- CSS
- · C++
- Javascript
- Java

Strengths

Time Management

Throughout study in University have had to meet project deadlines. I have gained experience at setting checkpoints, prioritizing task and planning timetables to ensure I get all work completed on time.

Problem Solving

Both math, computer science and software papers have built up my problem solving skills. Programming website also improved them as constantly overcoming small challenges.

Team Collaboration

Throughout study in University have had to meet project deadlines. I have gained experience at setting checkpoints, prioritizing task and planning timetables to ensure I get all work completed on

References

Margaret L Bailey (Data Entry)

Phone: 03 927 7613

Email: marglbailey@hotmail.com or: MargLBAllison@gmail.com Phil Marris (Dominoes)

Phone: 027 261 9483 Phone: 027 261 9483